<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
    xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
    <channel>
        <title>Mark Hartigan</title>
        <link>https://mchartigan.github.io/</link>
        <description>I'm a graduate research assistant at Georgia Tech studying spacecraft guidance, navigation, and control. I graduated from Purdue University with a B.S. in Aeronautical and Astronautical Engineering and a minor in Computer Science.</description>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 12:48:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <generator>rfeed v1.0.0</generator>
        <docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs>
        <item>
            <title>Making an RSS Feed for a Static HTML Site</title>
            <link>https://mchartigan.github.io/blog/20220118.html</link>
            <description>So I've been writing posts for my site in Emacs 27 as a way to familiarize myself with the interface -- in the event I need to use a text editor, I don't want to be completely out of my depth. I've come to realize, however, that I don't know how to program in Lisp. This poses somewhat of an issue when Emacs uses Lisp for any and all scripting and configuration. And you know what? I don't have any interest in learning Lisp! I have yet to encounter any other use case for it to convince me to invest the time, so I've concluded that I have better things to do with my time. Unfortunately, this decision promptly bit me in the ass when I wanted to add an RSS feed to my personal site.</description>
            <author> Mark Hartigan</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 23:21:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://mchartigan.github.io/blog/20220118.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Masala Gravy Recipe</title>
            <link>https://mchartigan.github.io/blog/20210805.html</link>
            <description>Goes great over rice or with naan! Paneer and vegetables go well to keep the recipe vegetarian.</description>
            <author> Mark Hartigan</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://mchartigan.github.io/blog/20210805.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Turning My Keyboard Into a Synth</title>
            <link>https://mchartigan.github.io/blog/20210216.html</link>
            <description>It's getting into the 5th week of my last semester at Purdue now, and you know what that means -- time to take way longer than I should to finish a project. Credit to Nicky Masso for this idea.</description>
            <author> Mark Hartigan</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://mchartigan.github.io/blog/20210216.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>New Year, New Website</title>
            <link>https://mchartigan.github.io/blog/20210101.html</link>
            <description>2020 was definitely a year for the history books: socially, politically, racially, environmentally, you name it.  But now's not the time for a retrospective -- all the issues of 2020 will still pursue us well into the new year and beyond. Rather, this post will be focusing on the insular world of my winter break before my last semester of college. Going in, I made several goals:</description>
            <author> Mark Hartigan</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://mchartigan.github.io/blog/20210101.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>How to Install Arch</title>
            <link>https://mchartigan.github.io/blog/20201015.html</link>
            <description>[NOTE] this guide has only been verified on a virtual machine, YMMV</description>
            <author> Mark Hartigan</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://mchartigan.github.io/blog/20201015.html</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>